Joshua E. Bunting

UniqueDragonsAre@gmail.com Personal Website: Shorturl.at/bpCHS

Summary

Seeking a position where I can utilize existing skills as an IT systems specialist, and further develop others. Help in an IT support environment to facilitate the day-to-day work of company employees.

Skills & Qualifications

- Adaptable/quick learner, Flexible, Personable and Self-Motivated
- > 3+ Years of Computer troubleshooting
- Google Javascript, HTML, CSS, and C++
- Windows, Android, Linux
- gSuite, Office
- > Fluent Spanish

Work Experience

Program Developer: Washington Kennewick Mission and Hulme Orthodontics & Dental Orthopedics, 11/2019 - Present

- 250% reporting performance increase by re-creating a data collection system to collect info from 230+ employees more efficiently.
- Allowing the company to collect and see live statistics and set effective goals for the future, but still keeping confidentiality and secure security policies for best information security.
- Provided direct end user operations support for the entire company.

App Developer: 2018-Present

- Independently Developed and published a mobile game on the Google Play store (Synth Ball)
- > 100+ people Installed and played
- Over 50 levels and 5 hours of gameplay

Janitorial + Handyman: American Academy of Innovation, South Jordan, Utah 2018 - 2019

- Manage small cleaning crew responsible for maintenance and repair at Middle and High school buildings and grounds. Duties include vacuuming, trash management, basic cleanup, mopping, dusting, window cleaning, and general repair.
- Accomplishing other various tasks occasionally during school times and over the weekends such as Os Installation, re-imaging, providing desktop and laptop support for students and teachers, as well as software, hardware, and other support in It systems.

Awards

- Innovator of the year
- Sterling Scholar in Computer Technology
- ➤ Eagle Scout

Education

- > ZeroToMastery.io, Full Stack Web Developer, Online, Present
- American Academy of Innovation 5410 W. South Jordan Parkway, South Jordan Utah 84009 10th-12th grade,2017-2019